in this video I'll show you how to
在这段视频中 我将向您展示如何
download shot cut on windows shotgun is
下载Windows上的快照剪辑是猎枪
a free and open source video editor
一个免费的开源视频编辑软件
let's just go to google and search shot
我们去谷歌上搜索一下照片吧
to cut all one word and the website
要删掉所有一个单词和网站
address is shot cut or I'll include the
地址是截图的 否则我会把
link in the description of this video
此视频描述中的链接
and go ahead and just click on downloads
然后继续 只需点击下载
so this is legitimately free software
所以这是合法的自由软件
but you have to be careful oh these are
但是你必须小心 哦 这些是
ads that are for something else this
这个广告是为其他东西做的
start now over here and these are gonna
现在从这里开始 这些将会
change it might be different for you
改变对你来说可能会有所不同
just make sure the actual download link
只需确保实际的下载链接
is a little confusing it's just a plain
有点令人困惑 这只是一个平淡的
text you can hover over and click on and
文本 您可以将鼠标悬停在其上并点击
so any of these would actually work
所以这些方法中的任何一个实际上都是可行的
you'll probably want to avoid the zip
你可能会想要避免拉链
and just get the Installer either the
只需获取安装程序或
64-bit or 32-bit and doesn't matter if
-位还是32位 如果是
you download it from site one or site -
你可以从第一站或第一站下载-
it's just multiple options to download
只有多个选项可供下载
from I'm gonna do it from site 2 which
我将从2号站点开始
is github and I'm gonna do the 64 bit
是GitHub和我要演的那部分
installer that'll probably be the best
那可能是最好的安装器
choice for you as well just keep in mind
你的选择也要记住
if you do have an older computer like
如果您确实有一台较旧的计算机 如
very old you'll want to do the 32-bit
非常老 你会想要做32位的
installer or maybe an older laptop or
安装者或可能是较旧的笔记本电脑或
something but most computers these days
有些东西 但现在大多数计算机
are 64-bit so this is downloading and
-比特 所以这是下载和
I'll pause the video and speed this up
我会暂停视频并加快播放速度
ok that's finished downloading now so I
好的 现在已经下载完毕 所以我
can see the Downloads on Firefox by
可以通过以下方式查看Firefox上的下载
clicking here and it shows me I can
点击这里 它向我展示了我可以
click this folder and it'll open up the
单击此文件夹 它将打开
location that it's saved on my computer
它保存在我的电脑上的位置
or I can just open up the file explorer
或者我可以直接打开文件资源管理器
and go to downloads which is where a
并转到下载 这是一个
downloaded on my computer and it's this
下载到我的电脑上 就是这个
shotcut - win 64 so I'll click on this
射击-赢得 所以我会点击这个
file and since it's not the zip it'll
文件 因为它不是压缩包 所以它将
just start installing right away so it
立即开始安装 这样它就可以
brings up the dialog I agree to the
显示我同意的对话框
terms and conditions I just leave
条款和条件 我刚离开
everything though at the defaults and
尽管一切都是默认的
click Next and install I'll speed this
点击下一步并安装 我会加快速度的
up to this part here ok there you have
到这一部分 好的 这里有
it so shotcut is now installed on my
所以ShotCut现在安装在我的
computer I can close out of all of these
我可以关闭所有这些计算机
and if I click the start button on my
如果我点击我的电脑上的开始按钮
computer and just type in shot cut it
电脑 只需输入镜头就可以了
comes up and I can create a desktop icon
然后我就可以创建一个桌面图标
for it too but here we have it so this
对它也是如此 但在这里我们有它 所以这个
is shot cut and I'll just show you real
是镜头剪辑 我会给你看真实的
quick just to get started so it starts
很快就开始了 所以它开始了
out with filters here but if we want to
这里没有过滤器 但如果我们想
change we can click on settings and and
更改我们可以点击设置和
we can go to layout and we can change -
我们可以去布局 我们可以改变-
this time
这一次
line project is kind of what this here
LINE项目在这里是什么意思
by default we can also go to layout and
默认情况下 我们还可以转到布局和
go to clip only so there's just some
只转到剪辑 这样就只有一些
different options here and there's also
这里和那里有不同的选择
restore default to layout if we want to
如果需要 请将默认设置恢复为布局
anything else a different dialogue you
还有什么不同的对话吗？
can click up here to toggle the history
可点击此处切换历史记录
being shown the peak meter being shown
显示的是峰值计量器
if something gets closed on the
如果某件事在
interface you can just click like
界面 您只需点击即可
Timeline up here to bring it back but to
时间线在这里把它带回来但是
get started with video you have to type
开始使用您必须键入的视频
in a project name and then we'll drag
在项目名称中 然后我们将拖动
some video in and you have to click on
一些视频 你必须点击
playlist that's the most important part
播放列表 这是最重要的部分
you can just go file open to if you do
如果需要 您可以直接打开文件
playlist you can actually drag in
您可以实际拖入的播放列表
multiple video files and there you have
多个视频文件 您就有了
it so that is a shot cut go ahead and
所以 这就是一个镜头剪辑 来吧
check out the tutorial series if you're
如果您正在学习系列教程 请查看
interested in learning how to use this
有兴趣学习如何使用这个
software more fully and check out other
更完整的软件 并查看其他
videos where I demonstrate free and open
我演示免费和开放的视频
source software of all qualities and
所有质量的源软件和
types thanks for watching catch you the
类型感谢收看捕捉到您的
next video
下一个视频